davisvision.com 2002-12-11

# Privacy and Security Policy

**Davis Vision, Inc. On-Line Privacy Policy**    

July 24, 2001 

At Davis Vision, Inc. ("Davis Vision"), we take the issue of privacy very seriously. We want to assure visitors to our web site that their information is secure and maintained in confidence. Please read through the following pages carefully. 

  1. Information Collected 
      1. General How you use the Davis Vision web site will determine whether or not we need to collect information from you, and how much information we collect.
The two ways you can use the web site are as a: 

              1. _Visitor_ – if you are casually browsing our web site and do not enter a User ID and Password issued by Davis Vision, you are a Visitor. 

              1. _Subscriber/Member_ \- if you subscribe to Davis Vision products and have a User ID and Password, you are a Subscriber/Member 

Davis Vision does not collect any personal information from Visitors. However, Visitors may voluntarily supply information in the form of an online feedback form or in an email.  
If you choose to become a Subscriber/Member, we may request basic personal information (for example, your name and email address).  

      2. Email and Product Inquiry
Davis Vision invites Visitors and Subscribers/Members to send email messages to Davis Vision regarding web site activities and Davis Vision products or services. Davis Vision retains copies of these email messages, but does not disclose email messages to any third parties.  
The information provided by a Visitor through the use of a feedback form will only be used by representatives who need to view this information to respond to the Visitor’s inquiry and to provide better customer service.  

      3. Use of Cookies  

A cookie is a small piece of information about an internet session that may be created when an individual accesses a web site. Davis Vision's web site, and certain sites it provides links to, use cookies to facilitate easier navigation within the sites and provide a higher level of convenience for users.  

Cookies can contain a variety of information, including the name of the web site that issued them,where on the site the user visited, passwords, and even user names and credit card numbers that have been supplied via forms. Note that most web browsers can be modified by the user to prevent cookies from being attached to the user. 

  2. Use of Information Collected 

All information submitted by any individual to Davis Vision may be retained to provide a record of such communications and to comply with any applicable legal and/or regulatory requirements. In addition:  

          * _Visitors_ \- Davis Vision uses information submitted by Visitors to its web sites only to respond to the inquiries and needs of those Visitors and to provide improved customer service.

          * _Subscribers/Members_ \- Davis Vision uses Subscribers'/Members' personally identifiable information, including medical data, collected by Davis Vision only for the purpose of providing vision care products and services to Subscribers/Members, unless the Subscriber/Member specifically grants permission to Davis Vision to use the information for additional purposes. 

          * Subscriber/Member information may also be "cleansed" by Davis Vision (stripped of any information which could identify you personally, such as your name or email addresses), aggregated with other data, and used for general research, marketing, or other purposes without permission, but only in non-individually identifiable forms.

III. Access to Information Collected   

    1. Associates

Certain Davis Vision associates may be provided with Visitor, Subscriber/Member information in order to respond to the individual's needs and provide requested information regarding specific products or services. Davis Vision associates are required, by written confidentiality agreements and corporate policies, to maintain the confidentiality of personal information and to use strict standards of care in handling the information of Davis Vision Visitors and Subscribers/Members. Associates who do not conform to these confidentiality requirements are subject to disciplinary sanctions that include dismissal. 

    2. Davis Vision Affiliates and Service Providers

Davis Vision may disclose personal information of its Visitors and Subscribers/Members to affiliates. Such information will be disclosed to respond to the individual's needs and to provide information about products or services offered by Davis Vision affiliates. Personal information is treated with the same standards of confidentiality that Davis Vision uses. Davis Vision affiliates are subject to Davis Vision's corporate policies and Davis Vision's non-related service providers are legally bound by contract to employ at least the same strict standards of confidentiality as employed by Davis Vision.

    3. Third Parties

Other than as set forth under B above, Davis Vision does not transmit any personal information collected through its web sites to any third party, including employers, without the consent of the individual. Personal information may be transmitted, however, if there is a specific need to complete a transaction requested by the individual. 

IV. Compliance Assurance   

    1. Security

Davis Vision uses commercially reasonable computer security technology selected and implemented to ensure adherence to the security and privacy policies described in this online posting. 

    2. Account Access
  
Davis Vision grants access to personal information only to those associates, affiliates and third parties as required to provide vision care products and services, or as permitted with your consent.  

    3. Questions and Concerns
  
If you have questions about this policy, or concerns regarding your personal information, please send us your question by clicking Contact Us on any of our web pages, or contact a customer service representative at 1-888-283-9374.  
DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY

WITH RESPECT TO DOCUMENTS AVAILABLE FROM THIS SERVER, NEITHER DAVIS VISION NOR ANY OF ITS EMPLOYEES MAKES ANY WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OR MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR ASSUMES ANY LEGAL LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, OR USEFULNESS OF ANY INFORMATION, APPARATUS, PRODUCT, OR PROCESS DISCLOSED, OR REPRESENTS THAT ITS USE WOULD NOT INFRINGE PRIVATELY OWNED RIGHTS. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT USE OF THIS WEB SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. DAVIS VISION SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE TO YOU FOR ANY CONTENT FOUND ON THIS WEB PAGE, NOR DOES DAVIS VISION MAKE ANY WARRANTY AS TO THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THIS WEB PAGE OR AS TO THE ACCURACY OR RELIABILITY OF ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THIS WEB PAGE. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM THE WEB PAGE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY.

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY CONTENT DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THIS WEB PAGE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGES TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS IN THE DOWNLOAD OF SUCH CONTENT.
